I just landed in Atlanta with one
mission to find a billionaire. And we're
not leaving until we do. Atlanta is home
to some of the wealthiest entrepreneurs
in [music] the world, billion-dollar
company founders, sports team owners,
and some of the richest people you've
never heard of. But here's the problem.
Billionaires don't just walk around with
name tags. So today, I'm going all over
the wealthiest part of Atlanta, walking
up to complete strangers trying to find
[music] the richest people I can find
because I refuse to stop filming until I
interview a billionaire. And if we
actually pull this off, we might uncover
some of the best wealth advice on the
planet. So, with that being said, let's
get this video on the way.
All right, guys. So, we made it to our
destination out here in Atlanta. We are
in Buckhead Village, where the
wealthiest people congregate. Man, look,
luxury stores, some of the nicest
restaurants in town. And look, the rules
of this video are very simple. I'm going
to go to the richest people that I can
see out here. I don't care how many
rejections it take. I don't care how
many millionaires that I have to run
into to find a billionaire and get the
secret advice on how to become wealthy
in today's world. So, come with us right
now and let's go find the richest people
in Atlanta. Excuse me, sir. Question for
you. How old were you when you became a
millionaire?
>> Okay, here we go.
>> Real quick. I have a channel with 24
million followers. Ma'am, I interviewed
Arthur Blank. I interviewed 60
billionaires.
>> Bank doesn't let me talk.
>> Excuse me, sir. How old were you when
you became a millionaire?
>> Oh, I can't.
>> So, we have a channel with 24 million
followers. I go all over the world
interviewing millionaires and
billionaires on their advice to the
younger generation. If there's one piece
of advice that you would give the
younger generation, we have 24 million
followers. What would that be, sir?
>> Go to school. And what did you study?
>> Yeah.
>> And college.
>> What was your What line of business were
you in?
>> I can't discuss that.
>> Okay. Could we get one minute with you?
>> No, thank you.
>> Okay, my man. Have a good one. Excuse
me, sir.
>> Question for you. How old were you when
you became a millionaire?
>> How old do you have?
>> How old were you?
>> No family.
>> So, we have a channel with 24 million
followers. I've interviewed over 60
billionaires in the last 5 years like
Arthur Blake, Mark Cuban, Michael Rubin.
I ask people on their best advice to
help the younger generation. If there's
one piece of advice from your career,
from all the wisdom, the experience
you've accumulated, what is the greatest
piece of advice you'd give the younger
generation?
>> Reading.
>> What was the number one book that
changed your life?
>> Well, of course, the Bible first and
then seven habits.
>> Highly effective. Stephen CVY,
>> right?
>> I love that. And when you talk about the
Bible, how important has faith been to
your success?
>> That's the cornerstone.
>> Cornerstone.
>> Five Fs. Faith, family, friends,
fitness, and finances.
>> And what was your main business? What
was your what was your main business?
>> Investments.
>> I just interviewed Bill Aman in New York
City. What? Yeah. What was the number
one investment that changed your life?
And like in today's world, the next one
to two years, what is the best industry
people should be investing in right now?
>> Just learning to learning a company,
understanding a company, and investing
in that business, public or private?
>> How big was your your biggest company?
>> Uh, too many to talk to.
>> I got you, my man. Have a good one, sir.
>> Excuse me, sir. Is that your
Rolls-Royce? How did you get rich, my
man?
>> What did you do to become wealthy? Real
quick, my man, I got 24 million
followers. I I've interviewed 60
billionaire. I don't know why.
>> Hey, boss man. Sir, do you know Aliko
Dangote?
>> Yeah,
>> I just interviewed him in Nigeria.
>> Can you please record me though?
>> Yes, sir. Real quick. Let me show you,
brother.
>> Hey, and look, that's just to show how
the people are being out here, man.
Look, it is not going to be easy to
interview these billionaires out here in
Nigeria. You guys, I mean, he was coming
out of a Rolls-Royce culling in. I mean,
you would think that, man, if that's the
kind of car that he's pulled up, man,
that he'd be receptive to at least give
some game to some people. But
nonetheless, man, we went for it. We're
going to keep on going, and I'm not
going to stop until I find the
wealthiest people out here in Atlanta,
Georgia. You guys, come on. Excuse me,
sir. Sir, question for you. How How did
you get rich? I have a I have a channel
with 24 million followers. I've
interviewed 60 billionaires in the last
5 years. What did you do?
>> Ah man. So when I was very young, I
became a Waffle House franchisee at 22
and I had 14 locations and then I'm also
in the hotel business in the home
furnishings business. So just being an
entrepreneur,
>> the Waffle House mogul.
>> Yeah, I did it for a long time.
>> Is it possible? I will tip your Uber
driver. Could I interview you? They're
not letting me film here, but right off
to the side here. Can we It's to help
the younger generation. I promise you we
got $24 million. Appreciate you asking,
but yeah, we we we've got plans
>> for one minute, please. I promise you
it's worth. We've interviewed Tom Cruz,
Arthur Blank, Mark Cuban, Tom Brady. For
one minute, just right off here, and I
promise you, and we'll let you get right
in here. Is that okay? I promise you,
we'll be so quick.
>> You're so kind and you're so good, but I
think we got to call it.
>> If there's one piece of advice you could
give to entrepreneurs in today's world
that want to build generational wealth
like yourself, what would that be?
>> Oh, that's a great question. What would
it be?
>> Obviously, the kind of the standard
answer is do what you love. And I think
you got to find the right thing because
if you chase the wrong thing, it's not
going to work for you. So you got to
find something that's going to want to
work. Want to make money and be the
right
>> How did you scale? You had 14 locations.
What did you do to scale in business?
What was your secret to scaling
companies?
>> You got to work every day and make sure
you pay attention to what's going on.
>> What was the best advice you ever
received throughout your career? If
there's one lesson a mentor, somebody
taught you about business or life, like
what is the greatest piece of advice you
ever received?
>> Greatest piece of advice I ever
received. I have to think about that. I
don't know, man. You just got to like
make it work. Make sure you make ends
meet. Make sure that you cash flow and
make sure that you stay productive.
>> Did you come from a lot of money?
>> No, we're working class.
>> What was your turning point to financial
freedom? How'd you get the money to buy
that first Waffle House?
>> My family got in the hotel business and
then from there we just kind of parlayed
forward.
>> I love that. Thank you.
>> Thank you for your time.
>> Thank you for I appreciate you.
>> I enjoy talking. You're good at what you
do. I'm sorry. I got a real big,
>> my bro. You're good, man. Nice to meet
you, bro. Have a good one, sir. Thank
you. Look, you guys, if there's one
lesson I'm trying to teach you in this
video, it is persistence. That guy
didn't get to 14 Waffle houses without
doing anything. Just like, man, I was
not going to get a couple answers out of
him if it wasn't for trying to be
persistent. Nonetheless, man, let's keep
this video rolling. We got to go find
another wealthy person out here in
Atlanta, Georgia. Guys, come on. Excuse
me, sir. How did you become wealthy?
>> Who said that? I'm wealthy.
>> You look like money, my man. I interview
billionaires all over the world. I got a
channel with 24 million followers. How
did you get rich?
>> Just working hard, man.
>> And what line of business?
>> My wife and I own some schools.
>> Schools? Like public schools? Private
schools or what?
>> Private schools.
>> You own the real estate. Like, what
makes the most amount of money in the
school business? actually the kids that
has to pay tuition.
>> What grade level is this? College,
university?
>> No, no, no, no. It's preschools.
>> How many do you own?
>> Two, but they're extremely large.
>> Congratulations, man. Did you have any
idea growing up that you were going to
own schools? I just I need I need just
30 seconds with you. I promise you this
is going to be so worth it, my man. I
promise you. We got We just interviewed
Aliko Dangote in Africa. We we've
interviewed 60 billionaires like Tom
Cruz, Arthur Blank, Tom Brady to help
the younger generation. I'll show you
the channel right after. Did you come
from money growing up?
>> No.
>> No. So, what was your turning point to
becoming financially free? Is it a
moment in your life where you were like,
I want to go out there and really build
an empire for myself and for my family?
>> Just didn't want to work for nobody
else. So, entrepreneuring is kind of
like in my DNA and I just knew I had to
find something.
>> Why the education business though? Why
schools?
>> Uh, somebody just introduced me to it in
Florida.
>> You had good mentors.
>> Yeah. What was the greatest piece of
advice you ever got throughout your
career? If there's one lesson that a
mentor, somebody taught you about
business, what's the greatest piece of
advice you ever received throughout your
career?
>> Take care of your employees.
>> Take care of your employees. So, is it
more important to talk to take care of
the employee? The
>> store about to close.
>> One minute. I promise you, my man.
>> I promise you, man. Is this your wife
right here? How important is the
decision to marry the right woman in
today's world? Because look, we've seen
a lot.
>> The number one thing, period. I couldn't
have done nothing without it.
>> So, let me ask you this right here
though. A lot of men, they make the
mistake of choosing the right life
partner, and their business empire can
crumble. How did you know that was the
What's the number one quality that you
look for in your partner that told you
that, hey, that's the one that I'm going
to marry?
>> God told me. That's why it's been 30
years.
>> So, you believe in God? I do.
>> Who is your God?
>> Jesus Christ. How did you know Jesus was
real? Tell me, man. I promise you.
>> It got brought to me. Hey, I felt it in
my spirit.
>> Okay, so let me ask you this right now.
At your school, what was the most amount
of money you made in a single year?
>> Close to 2 million.
>> Close to $2 million, man. How about this
last question?
>> Your best sales and negotiation advice
for anybody in business in today's
world?
>> Be sellable.
>> Thank you, my man. I appreciate What's
your name, sir? I'd love I'd love to
connect and amplify what you're doing.
Got to connect with you real quick.
>> Watch. They closed at six.
>> I got you, my man. I got you. What was
your name?
>> Sean. I'm going to shake your hand real
quick. Thank you, sir. How do you feel
about AI?
>> I'm old, so AI is new to me. Have have
have you heard about High Level though?
>> I've heard.
>> It's a business software that people
like you, you can put into your business
and what you can do is automate your
entire follow-up process with all your
prospective students, your clients, and
whatnot. It's called High Level. And all
the most successful entrepreneurs in
today's world are using in their
business to help scale and grow their
businesses cuz you can reach out to your
clients automatically. You've got to
check it out. All right, last one. How
old are you today?
>> 59.
>> Okay, last one. If Look, if me and you
died tomorrow and you could leave one
last guiding principle with the younger
generation, what would that be? One last
message right here.
>> God,
>> one more, man. Come here.
>> That was it. Was that ridiculous or
what? Bro, guys, we just interviewed a
multi-millionaire who made over $2
million in a single year from owning
what preschools, he said. And we're
headed right now to go find our next
interview to go find the billionaire out
here in Atlanta. But before we do that,
I want you to understand something. It
does not matter what business you're in.
You could own a preschool, you could own
a plumbing company, you could own a
marketing agency. Every business needs
the same thing in the age of AI. More
leads, better follow-up, and great
systems that keep everything organized.
And that's exactly why I was telling him
about High Level. High Level is the
all-in-one sales and marketing platform
that replaces all the softwares, the
five, six different softwares that
business owners are paying for and
wasting a ton of money on. High Lee in
one place gives you a CRM. It helps you
build a calendar, funnels, email and
text marketing, appointment reminders,
and automated follow-up all in one
place. So, when a potential customer
reaches out, they book an appointment or
fills out a form, High Level can
automatically follow up with them so you
never lose a single dollar on the table.
Because the truth is, guys, most
businesses do not need another tool.
They need a system that connects
everything together. And remember, it
does not matter whether you own one
preschool or 100 different businesses.
The systems are what allow you to scale.
So, waste no more time. Go down, click
the link in the description of this
video to start your free trial using
High Level today and watch your business
change forever and take off. With that
being said, let's go find a billionaire
out here in Atlanta. Excuse me, sir.
Sir, how did you get rich?
>> Reco?
>> Yes, man. We got a channel with 24
million followers. I go all over the
world and interviewing billionaires. How
did you get rich about people like that,
bro?
>> Now, how did you get rich, man? I'm
going all over Atlanta interviewing the
richest people. What'd you do? I can
tell, man. You look like money, man.
What' you do?
>> I learned about wealth and investing in
the prison cell, bro.
>> So, you went to prison?
>> Went to prison when I was 16 for attempt
murder on Robert, man. Did 10 years.
>> Are you serious?
>> I did 10 years, man.
>> And what do you do now?
>> Investor. Got a couple companies, got
some real estate, you know, just playing
a wealth game now, bro.
>> 100%. So, how old were you when you
became a millionaire?
>> Probably about How you know I'm a
millionaire, bro?
>> I can tell, man. I can tell.
>> Probably about 35.
>> How old are you now?
>> 44.
>> What was the most amount of money you
made in a single year? Nah, I don't talk
about money like that, bro.
>> Give me a range real quick. So, I've
interviewed over 60 billionaires in the
last 5 years. I I ask everybody that
question. How much did you make in one
year? Just Just tell it. Give us a
range.
>> I bought my freedom back. Let's say
that.
>> Give me a range. How much?
>> I did eight figures.
>> More than $10 million.
>> Oh, you asked too much, man. [laughter]
>> You made more than 10 million in a year.
>> I made enough, man. Eight figures. I'm
going to leave you with that. Are you
serious?
>> I still got people in the hood. I got to
go to the hood all the time, man.
>> Can I interview you for one minute real
quick? It's to help the younger
generation.
>> Yeah. I know who you are, man. You good
people, man.
>> We could do that, bro.
>> For sure.
>> Did you come from money, man? Did you
come from a lot of money? Nah, man. Born
and raised in New Orleans. Was homeless
at 13. Man, my mom's went to prison.
Grandmother went to prison. I went to
prison at 16. What did you learn about
people in prison? Man, everybody has an
agenda in prison, man. Prison doesn't
really help you become better. You got
to take it upon yourself to be better.
>> What's your best self-improvement advice
for anybody right now starting out in
business, right? Like, you didn't come
from a rich family, but yet you broke,
you escaped poverty, man. You made it
happen. What's your best
self-improvement? The number one
actionable step anybody can take to get
rich in today's world.
>> Keep going. And the reason why I say
that is because when I was in prison, I
had a vision when a guy taught me about
investing. He said that wealthy people
stop telling their time for money.
Wealthy people learn how to give value
to people and wealthy people learn how
to make their money work for them. And
so once I learned how to make my money
work for me, it was a game changer for
me. And the stock market was the first
place I could see my money move that
fast outside of the streets.
>> I need you give me a secret right here.
What do the richest people in the world
do with their money? How does somebody
actually make their money work for them
in today's world?
>> Invest in the best companies in America.
Right now, we investing in Nvidia. We
investing in Google. We're investing in
Palunteer. Everything that's making the
world move forward. We in a new era
right now. And I feel like if the person
is not investing right now in the
market, they are missing like somebody
in the '90s will be missing the
internet. Think about that. And so we
see everything that's moving forward. We
see the stock market. We see these
companies that we use every single day,
but why don't we own them? And that's
one of the things that hurt us when it
come to poverty. We don't learn about
ownership. Ownership is the key to
wealth.
>> You got you got to have ownership.
>> You got to have ownership. Without
ownership, you'll always be the slave to
somebody else's dream.
>> So, what was the most amount of money
you made in a single day?
>> 1.1 million.
>> No, I know you did not.
>> 1.1 million from trading. I made a good
trade. It was on Nvidia last year before
the split.
>> Are you serious?
>> Yeah, that was my best trades on my post
right now. $1.1 million, man.
>> So, do you think stocks are better than
real estate?
>> I think that both are needed. I think
stock is stocks are good to increase
your wealth. Real estate is good to down
pay your taxes. So, one of my best years
of 2024. I did make eight figures. So, I
had to buy a $5.5 million business. So,
I can write that off.
>> This is game segregation. And I had to
learn that real time. So the money that
you put in the building, you get to
write that off. So I was able to write
that off.
>> Do you pay a lot of money in taxes?
>> Man, listen.
>> How much you pay in taxes? Tell me.
>> My biggest year in taxes, I paid $4
million in paid $4 million in taxes and
$600,000 in state taxes. But again, when
you're learning about money, nobody
tells you that. So that was I use that
as my tuition of being wealthy. So I
didn't get mad at it. I learned it. I w
up getting a CPA and I learned about
cost structure, tax structure, how to
structure my businesses, how to write
stuff off, how to start a charity. So
those are the things that I learned
later on in the game. What do the
wealthiest people do to avoid taxes?
Give me your number one tax hack the
wealthiest people know.
>> Commercial real estate and charity.
Create a nonprofit organization, connect
it to your building. You can donate 10%
of your revenue from each company to
your nonprofit organization. Nonprofit
organization then gets to handle the
business. You get to write that off and
then the nonprofit organization then can
hire you to staff their event. And so
that's one of the most amazing ways to
reduce taxes.
>> You know that they don't teach us in
school, right?
>> That's the purpose, man. They can't
teach us that in school because if they
taught you that in school then you would
you wouldn't be a financial slave
>> in the next one to two years. What's the
best industry people should be getting
into right now?
>> Cyber security and AI. And the reason
why you say cyber security because as we
get into cyber, as we see AI growing, as
we see technology growing, like there's
not even people working in storage no
more. So hackers get heavy. So cyber
security goes up. The government just
signed a $17 billion deal for cyber
security. So why not invest in cyber
security and the next thing would be
100% AI. We we can't go without it.
>> So you do your homework. Oh man, I'm a
living breathing homework machine. Man,
>> are you are you a big reader?
>> Heavy. That's one of the things I
learned from prison man. Frederick
Douglas said something that I really
love. He said once a man gets
information, it makes it hard for him to
be a slave.
>> Information changes situations only
through implementation.
>> And it changes the conversation, the
conversation changes your compensation.
>> This is gate right here. [laughter] You
hear that? Right.
>> I have a saying. Poor people live check
to check. Rich people live year to year.
Wealthy people live from generation to
generation because they learn how they
buy time back. And once you buy your
time back, you can do whatever you want
to do.
>> Or you're a South by you. [laughter]
>> And listen, if you allow them to feed
you, you give them permission to starve
you. And so if you dependent on the job,
and I'm not saying everybody made to be
entrepreneurs, but if you dependent on
that one source of income, then that
becomes financial suicide. And then you
already know like we can't depend on a
government to just feed us. There's two
playbooks. There's a playbook that they
teach you and there's a playbook that
they live by. Why not use the playbook
that they live by? Cuz the one that they
teach us is only allowed to make them
get richer and us get poor.
>> So is it better to be a business owner
or an investor in today's world? I think
the investor cuz everybody not built to
be a business owner. Business can be
taxing and I'm not talking about from
dollar perspective just on a mental and
a physical but as an investor you get to
let somebody else do the hard work and
you get to use your money to invest in
their dream and then their dream pays
you
>> 100%. You get equity in that.
>> Equity is freedom.
>> What was the number one book that
changed your life? The number one book
anybody watching right now needs to read
if they want to get rich in today's
world.
>> The number one book I read that changed
my life was the Bible.
>> So you believe in God?
>> Oh man. Deuteronomy 8:18 says God gives
us the ability to produce wealth. Man,
>> God does want us to be rich.
>> Oh, God ain't never told us to be broke.
>> And even when we think about Christ,
man, Christ gave us 37 parables. 16 of
them was about money, business, how to
deal with greed, how to steward money.
And so, I think that's just a part of
the Bible that people don't read. And if
me and you died tomorrow and you could
leave one last message with the younger
generation, what would that be?
>> If you don't prepare the generation
today to be successful, then they'll be
the next financial slaves. Nobody ever
gave us wealth, but the wealthy people
learn how to consistently pass down not
just money, but information. And so, you
create what's called family SOPs. It's
the blueprint that your family have to
live by when you gone. In the movie
Black Panther, it says that a man's
greatest job is to prepare his seeds to
live and succeed when he's gone.
>> Can I tell you something? Talk to me,
bro. You
>> got amazing advice, F.
>> Thank you, brother. I appreciate you for
your time, man.
>> Guys, that's got to be one of the best
interviews I've ever done in Hard Knocks
history out here in Atlanta. And he made
eight figures in a single year. He just
gave us the real blueprint on how to use
Wall Street in the stock market to
become a millionaire in today's world.
But look, you remember the premises. You
remember the rules of this video. We are
not going to stop filming till I find a
billionaire out here. So, the search
continues. Let's keep the hunt going,
you guys. Come on.
>> Excuse me, sir. Sir, question for you.
How old were you when you became a
millionaire?
>> How do you know I'm a millionaire?
>> You look like money, man. I interview
billionaires all over the world. How old
were you?
>> I was uh 26.
>> And what lot of business were you in?
How how did you get rich?
>> Healthcare.
>> You're in the healthare. Are you a
business owner?
>> Oh, yeah. I own over 22 companies in
healthcare.
>> Are you serious? And what was the most
amount of money you made in a single
year across the companies?
>> Well, last year we did $3 billion a year
>> with a B.
>> With a B.
>> Are you a billy dare?
>> Yeah.
>> You are. Yeah.
>> Can I interview you for a minute? I go
all over the world to even billionaires
to help the younger generation.
>> Sure. Did you come from money growing
up? Did you come from a lot of money?
>> Oh, no. I was in I lived in the projects
my whole life. I didn't have a father.
My mother was sixth grade educated
waitress. Went into foster care when I
was 13 and went into five different
foster careers, eight different
elementary schools, five different high
schools. Had to at 19 years old drop out
of school because I didn't have the
money.
>> So, you did not have rich parents.
>> Oh, absolutely not. We were scraping by
just to get food.
>> What was your turning point to financial
freedom? What was that moment in your
life early on where you were like, I'm
meant for more?
>> I was 20 and uh they wouldn't hire me
because I didn't have a degree. And I
asked them, well, what would somebody
with a degree make? And they said, well,
$1,100 a month and 33 to 50% commission.
And I said, well, what if I work for no
money a month and just 33% straight
commission? Would you give me a chance?
A year later, I bought the firm and I've
always owned my own firm ever since
then.
>> Are you a good salesman?
>> I was. I I probably still am.
>> What is your secret to sales? It's like
back in the business world when you were
closing deals, what was your number one
sales and negotiation advice to any
entrepreneur?
>> Well, the number one thing is that you
can have everything in the world you
want if you help other people get what
they want. So, what I did is try to find
out what was the win for the person I
was talking to. I didn't try to sell
them what I was doing. I basically asked
them what did they need and then I
fulfilled that need. And um that's the
definition of a good business.
>> The more money you make other people,
the more money you're going to make
yourself.
>> Yeah. But it's not my money. It's God's
money.
>> So, you believe in God?
>> Oh, absolutely. When I went in a foster
home, I was always by myself when I was
at home. And but when I went in a foster
home, there were five kids and it was
just the loudest room in the the world.
And then they sat down, got quiet, held
hands, then they said a prayer, and I
said, "That's what I want when I grow
up." And so I've always maintained that.
And um and I think God has prepared me
for what I'm about to do now.
>> What are you doing now?
>> I'm running for governor of Georgia.
>> Are you actually?
>> Yeah, absolutely.
>> What's your name?
>> Rick Jackson.
>> And how old are you?
>> I'm 72.
>> You're not 72? You look so young at 72.
>> Well, well, thank you. I I appreciate
that. Any other questions you want me
I'll they I'll tell you anything after
you nice like that.
>> 100% [clears throat] my baby. Are you a
big reader? Did you read a lot of books?
>> I read a lot of executive summaries and
uh books and so forth.
>> Is there one book recommendation you
have for anybody that's starting out
wanting to build? You know,
>> it's a book called What They Don't Teach
You at Harvard and it was by a Harvard
grad who started IMG, the management
group that has all Jack Nicholas, all
those brands and so forth. And what it
basically they don't teach you at
Harvard is how to deal with people.
>> You know the secret, man. What do people
not understand about people? What's the
most interesting thing that you've
learned about how to deal with people?
>> I was coaching football um in 1981 and
it rained one day and so I put everybody
in the room and waiting on their parents
and I said okay let's do it. What is
your goal? And everybody answered it
right. They said win the national
championship. I said okay why do you
want to do that? And I got 22 different
reasons. One of them said I want to have
a girlfriend. I want friends and all
that. So next day, uh, the guy wasn't
blocking right and I said, you know,
Bob, you'll never get a girlfriend if
you don't block better than that. So you
have to look at what people what they
want and that you're more interested in
them and helping them than you are
yourself. Once you do that, you unlock
the power of being able to help somebody
else.
>> You know that they don't teach this in
school, right?
>> That's right. It's I call it street
smarts. I used to scout tickets down at
Georgia Tech when I was 12 years old, 11
and 12. And so I learned how to deal
with people doing that. So you always
had that entrepreneurial seat in you.
>> Very much so. I had a paper out when I
was, you know, 10 years old. And
>> John Morgan, who's Morgan and Morgan,
he's a good friend of mine and that's
what he says the most successful people.
He had a paper out when he was growing
up.
>> Yeah. Well, I mean what you do is that I
was out of control of my childhood and I
I was selling I did bag groceries for 25
an hour. I got a $525 check. I was 10
years old and it said I I said I can do
anything I want to with that $5. I have
control. So I equated money with the
ability to control my life. nobody else.
I don't care about controlling anybody
else, but I do believe in controlling
myself and so I associated that with it.
>> So, who taught you business? I mean,
obviously, I know that you mentioned you
had street smarts, but I mean, to be
able to build a multi-billion dollar
company, you didn't have rich parents.
Where did you learn your business from?
>> Oh, I've studied everything. I mean,
there's nobody that knows more about
tax, marketing, and uh accounting and
all these things because I always just
ask question. I never would abdicate to
any professional lawyer or anybody. I
wanted to know as much. So I my
non-deree is very expensive. In 1980 I
was 26 years old and I hired a PhD from
Georgia State to teach me everything for
$2,000 a month and teach me everything
about business that a MBA or PhD would
have. So I because I was so insecure
without having a degree. I had an
unending thirst for knowledge. The main
thing I've done is I never saw myself as
a victim. A lot of people blame
everybody else when they fail. I don't
blame anybody but me because I want
control. I can't control anybody else. I
can only control myself. So when you
take ownership of your failures and you
learn from them and then get up one more
time then you fall down. That's my
definition of success.
>> That's how you escape poverty.
>> Absolutely.
>> Can I tell you something?
>> Yeah.
>> You have amazing advice, sir.
>> Well, thank you.
>> Thank you for your time, my friend. And
I like
>> What's your name?
>> I'm James.
>> James. I I connect with all the
billionaires that I interview. Could I
get your contact?
>> Uh, absolutely.
>> Guys, that's a wrap on today's video. I
need y'all to stop right now, like and
subscribe for amazing content coming
every week to the School of Hard Knocks.
We just interviewed some of the
wealthiest people in all of Georgia. But
I want to go a step further and connect
you directly with the wealthiest people
in my network. Give you access to the
billionaires I interview on live calls I
host every single week inside of my
private entrepreneur community, the
school of mentors. You can join right
now by going down to the link in the
description of this video and get access
to live calls every week with the 8,
nine, and 10 figureure entrepreneurs
that I interview. So I can't wait to see
you on the inside. With that being said,
we'll see you in the next